[{"answer": "\"Meet the Fockers.\"", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Probably -- one of the \"Night at the Museum\" maybe?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, that's the big question that we're all waiting for.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Where do you think the depth charge will come in the scandal if at all?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Well, we don't discuss our sources.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, to the extent that he has said that one of the reasons that this is coming up is because of race, it seems to me that he's using race as a propaganda weapon here.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Let me start with you, Randall Kennedy, is Herman Cain playing the race card or is the race card being played against him here?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "I think that's right.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Larry Elder, would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, the people who like him like him a whole lot and I think that they are rallying to their man.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Yes, it's been nonpolitical if you like, but there is something very human about Herman Cain which is resonating with people, isn't there?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "No, I think what's shown is that, you know, people have their bases and people who like politicians are willing to close their eyes to, you know, deficiencies for their man.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "I mean is there one rule for as some believe black conservative politicians and another rule for middle class white politicians?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Maybe it's not really you.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "What is the idea of me?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "I like doing that.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "The need to delve deep in people's souls?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "And actually you like doing that.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Do you like the pressure of having to be funny?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "\"Meet the Fockers.\"", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Probably -- one of the \"Night at the Museum\" maybe?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "What did you do, Focker?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, it depends what you're talking about.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Advantage or disadvantage?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "But then there's also -- then you have to kind to make your own way and, you know?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "They'd be married 57 years?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "It's pretty amazing?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "No, that's true.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, they -- first of all they're not that interested in watching my movies.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Are there some you don't let them watch?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "They are -- they're very theatrical children, yes.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Are they showing signs of comedic genius?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "I love being a father.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Do you love being a father?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "You have to figure out how you're going to do it so that you make sure that you have the family time.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Yes, I mean, in terms of your filming schedule, how do you juggle that with being a dad?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "There's no darkness.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "I can't find the demons?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "It's well hidden.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Major drug abuse?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Brian Grazer and I are having an affair.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Anything to chip away at the halo?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I'm in love with his hair.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Is it going well?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "I was laughing that you always show the person watching themselves.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Why are you laughing there?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "I'm really excited because it's actually -- it's a genre of movie that I've never been in.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "\"Tower Heist\"?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Oh wow.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What's going on with your country?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I -- I'm a -- I'm disappointed that we haven't seen more bold decisions from him and a willingness, I think, to maybe stick to more of what he had, in his campaign, had said in terms of what he was willing to do.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "He disappointed you, Obama?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I went down there for the first time before the earthquake, and it was in such a bad situation that I wanted to try to do something to help there.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "I mean, why does it still motivate you?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, I think everybody's entitled to their opinion.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "What do you feel about people who criticize celebrities for helping the stuff like that, the criticism being you're just doing it to promote yourself?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "You must be sick of it, aren't you?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Sometimes I'm sick of it.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Are you being honest?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Wait a minute.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "-- with the passage of time?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Both.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "I'm affectionate toward the movie or the passage of time in general?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Now it comes out.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Any tantrums?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "It's like a nightmare.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "-- monstrous, box office megastar?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Not that I have found.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "For the worse in any way, a little chink in the armor that we could do?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Die.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Then what will you do?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Things you've heard.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "You mean bad things about him?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "As far I'm concerned, he is.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Is he as -- is he as squeaky clean as he's trying to make out?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "I'm sure there's --", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Is anybody, do you think, in Hollywood, left who's got a better record than that?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Would he beat that?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Put it this way: we developed the movie -- Brian and I developed the movie for several years.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "How important is someone like Ben to a movie now?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "If it doesn't work out, it all becomes his fault?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Yes, total of six movies.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "And Brian had done maybe five, six movies with him?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "Ben wasn't -- no, this was after we wrapped the movie.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 727, "question": "Ben was not available?", "qSentId": 726}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "Did he -- did he, someone like you, feel intimidated?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "Yes, because Eddie has been -- he's iconic for, you know, the last 25 years.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "Working with someone like that?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "We've got it.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "Get Leo in a dress?", "qSentId": 783}, {"answer": "I can't do it.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "(INAUDIBL) get people from the acting world together, I'm always fascinated who is the actor's actor, who's the one -- if you could cast one leading man in the last movie you ever make, who would it be?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "In a movie, my first movie role.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 803, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 802}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 806, "question": "It is a Robert Zemeckis movie?", "qSentId": 805}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111103pmt", "aSentId": 808, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 807}]